<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Varnio Technologies</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Varnio Technologies</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 00:06:58 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Farshid Varno</title>
      <link>/team/farshid/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 00:06:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/team/farshid/</guid>
      <description>Web Page Resume (HTML) Resume (PDF) I am a Machine Learning Eng. &amp;amp; Researcher with a strong technical background in HW &amp;amp; SW co-design. I&amp;rsquo;m a team player who strives building new technologies. In summary I am:
🏗️ The creator of FedSim Simulator (https://fedsim.varnio.com) 💡 The first inventor of an international patent on Transfer Learning 🧐 A reviewer for top ML conferences like ECCV, CVPR, ICCV 🎓 A Doctoral Candidate at Dalhousie University (https://dal.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FedSim</title>
      <link>/products/fedsim/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/products/fedsim/</guid>
      <description>FedSim is a generic Federated Learning simulator. See the latest documentation at this link.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Research</title>
      <link>/services/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Nov 2018 12:33:46 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/research/</guid>
      <description>To get the best out of your data, we are commited to provide summary, analysis and report of the knowledge you can extract from your data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Federated Learning</title>
      <link>/services/fl/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:14:39 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/fl/</guid>
      <description>We provide vision and expertise to build Federated Learning systems for wide range of applications.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Consultation</title>
      <link>/services/consaltation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Nov 2018 15:15:26 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/services/consaltation/</guid>
      <description>We have the tools that can exactly tell you whther to go for a collect and learn appraoch or distributed learning.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Feb 2018 17:01:34 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Lorem markdownum aequalis strigis. Saetigeri iubeas, vultu huic alvum nondum de obside ut laniavit arbor palmis, cum quin. Rupes vetat videndo, armigerae crimen habet Priamum nec.
Ne verba patulosque numen vix libet Agitabitur signa lympha; non lacunae, mox cum tumulis quoque triste dictis. Ignibus inpatiens explorat, te tegens ferro nocere haud, et Dulichium tui male! Quo sed fuit flexit et hic die solido, gloria?
Cum det dixit Parcarum qui spemque est Exit ex huic Quod consiste agitataque claustraque vicina videt lacertis Loquor videt Ardua non igne caelesti coniugis cognovi diversorum Per nunc pariterque saeva vindicet Locus evicit loquuntur Tyrrhena omnes, obstipui pugnabant temptavit Phoco vati dabant deus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Farshid Varno</title>
      <link>/resume/farshid/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resume/farshid/</guid>
      <description>Intro I am a Machine Learning Eng. &amp;amp; Researcher with a strong technical background in HW &amp;amp; SW co-design. I&amp;rsquo;m a team player who strives building new technologies. In summary I am:
The creator of FedSim Simulator The first inventor of an international patent on Transfer Learning A reviewer for top ML conferences like ECCV, CVPR, and ICCV A Doctoral Candidate at Dalhousie University and I have:
4+ years experience as Research Scientist (industrial) 1+ years experience as Data Scientist and Research Assistant (academic &amp;amp; industrial) 2 years experience as FPGA Engineer/RTL Designer (industrial) Experience Research &amp;amp; Industry Consultant, ML Engineer, Varnio Tech.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
